Guide to the Sala Udin Papers, 1980-2005 AIS.2006.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh Works, 1985-2004; X.
  - City Controller Flaherty - Special Reports, 1997, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Stadium Lease Comparisons with 15 U.S. Cities for Major League Baseball, May 1999; 2.
  - Hotel and RAD taxes, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Job Training, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Labor - Department of Labor Statistics materials, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Labor - Petitions, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Legal research, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Minorities and Women - Affirmative Action Program Planning Data report, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Minorities and Women - Builders Guild Minority Perception Study, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Minorities and Women - Equal Opportunity Commission, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Minorities and Women - MBE and WBE compliance, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Minorities and Women - M/WBE contracting opportunities at PNC Park Project, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Minorities and Women - Minority Business Enterprise draft proposal, February 6, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Policy - Policy statement (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Policy - Policy analysis, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Public Auditorium Authority by-laws and statutes, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Public hearings and post-agenda meetings, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Research - Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Research - Boston/Camden, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Research - Boston/Camden - M/WBE participation and resident jobs policy, 1985-1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Research - Dade County and Philadelphia, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Section 3 Federal, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Section 3 HUD, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Turner Construction Company, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Plan B, 1995-2003; XI.
  The Plan B series focuses on the Plan B controversy in Pittsburgh beginning in 1998. The Pittsburgh Steelers (NFL) and the Pittsburgh Pirates (MLB) shared Three Rivers Stadium. The "Plan B" proposal included building two new stadiums (Heinz Field and PNC Park) in addition to an expansion of the David L. Lawrence Convention Center. On July 9, 1998, the plan was approved by the Regional Authority Board for $809 million. Sala Udin was a chairman of the Plan B Oversight Committee which was able to provide several of the construction contracts to businesses owned by city residents, minorities, and women.
  The Plan B series and the Women and Minority Business Enterprise (WMBE) series contain similar holdings because many jobs related to Plan B construction were performed by WMBE certified businesses. This series includes materials regarding Plan B to and from Councilman Sala Udin, the Chair of the Plan B Oversight committee. It includes documents surrounding the creation of the committee, correspondence to and from Pittsburgh citizens, organizations, and businesses, information about contracts, bids, and employment, news releases and articles, WMBE certification procedures for Plan B jobs, meeting minutes and agendas, agreements, project updates, Sports and Exhibition Authority documentation, statistics regarding minorities and women in Pennsylvania, and a petition for the reestablishment of magisterial districts. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - African American and Women Board Members of Economic Development Organizations in the Pittsburgh Region, July 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - African American Labor Development Coalition, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - African American Workers Union, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Arena Group, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Arlyn Corporation, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Balaba Concrete Supply, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Bidwell Technical Services, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Builders' Guild of Western Pennsylvania, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Certification of MBE/WBE, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Contracts and employment, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Contracting Management Services, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Executive Summary on Black and White Economic Conditions, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Founding of Plan B Oversight Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - M/WBE contracts and bids, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - MBE/WBE outreach meeting, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Minutes and agenda of Plan B Oversight Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NAACP, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Minority Contractors - Contractors Success Series, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Negro Baseball League in Pittsburgh (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - News releases and coverage, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Office of Democratic Legislative Information, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Opportunities and Issues for MBE/WBE Procurement presentation (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Petition for Reestablishment of Magisterial Districts, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Pirates Plan presentation (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Pretrial statement in Walter E. Jackson v. Dick Corporation, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Project Stabilization Agreement for Pittsburgh Steelers Stadium, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Project updates, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sports and Exhibition Authority, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sports and Exhibition Authority Final Report, July 2001 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - The Status of Women in Pennsylvania, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Working Group, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Subject Files, 1980-2005; XII.
  The Subject Files series includes materials from a variety of topical sources of interest to Sala Udin personally, politically, and professionally. Subjects include: individuals, organizations, locations, City Council photographs, programs, and Udin's time as a presidential electorate/DNC representative as well as his election and reelection materials. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - 92nd Infantry Division WWII Association, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action - Benchmark Pittsburgh Post-Gazette reports, clippings, correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action - Policy, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Africa - Congress of African People, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Africa - National Summit on Africa, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Africa - National Summit on Africa - Clippings (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Africa - National Summit on Africa - Participants and mailing information, 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Africa - National Summit on Africa - Policy Plan, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Africa - Trade Center/Mission for South Africa and the Democratic Republic of the Congo, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - African American Organizations - African American Chamber of Commerce, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - African American Organizations - African American Leadership Committee and Black Think Tank, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - African American Organizations - African American Leadership Renaissance - Correspondence, legislation, memoranda, and minutes, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - African American Organizations - National Black Caucus of Local Elected Officials (NBC-LEO) - Directories, by-laws, and newsletters, 1995-2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - African American Organizations - National Forum for Black Public Administrators, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Black history resources, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Brilliant Lighting Design, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Cable TV Advisor Committee - Regarding the Cable Transfer Resolution, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Campbell Tiu Campbell report, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Capital Assets court transcripts, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Library - Board meetings and materials, 1997-2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Library - Martin Luther King Reading Center, 1986-2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Museum, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Museum of Art - Board Meeting, April 5, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Center for Family Excellence, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - The Children's Home of Pittsburgh, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Churches - Central Baptist Church, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Churches - Southwest Pennsylvania churches, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Churches - Ebeneezer Baptist, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Churches - Epiphany Catholic, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Churches - Grace Memorial Presbyterian, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Churches - Macedonia FACE, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Churches - Warren Methodist, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - City Source Associates - Regarding clean-up of publically owned lots, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Civic Cards - The City of Pittsburgh Classic Set, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Civics 101 - City Service for Artists, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Comcast - Communications Workers of America AFL-CIO, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Community Development Block Grant funds and requests, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Community Partners Institute - Find the Rivers, 2003-2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dakota Street Wall, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Directories and member lists of various organizations, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Disability Agenda - Agendas, correspondence, minutes, and neighborhood sector vendors, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Disability Agenda - Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Disability Agenda - Visibility of Pittsburgh, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Duncan Playground Rehabilitation contract report, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Female Offenders Program, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Foundations - The Jerome Bettis Bus Stops Here Foundation (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Foundations - Shaunte Betts Foundation, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Foundations - Rudy Bruner Award, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Foundations - Roberto Clemente Foundation, 1998-2005 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Foundations - The Forbes Funds, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Foundations - Henry George Foundation, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Foundations - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1997-2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Foundations - Pittsburgh Foundation, circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Friends of Zeiss, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Guyasuta Fellowship, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Heinz Endowment, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Hill House, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Home Value - Southwest Home Equity, 1992-2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - House of the Crossroads drug and alcohol treatment services, 1980-2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - House of the Crossroads drug and alcohol treatment services, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Kennard Summer Basketball League, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Living wage, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Maglev - Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Maglev - Keystone Minority Capital Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Maglev - Meetings, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Maglev - Newspaper and press releases, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Maglev - Pittsburgh Airborne Shuttle System (PASS), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Maglev - Plans and proposal summaries, 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Maglev - Opposition, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - MLB All-Star Game (3 b/w prints), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - MLK Task Force, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Lou Mason Senior Housing, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Mattress Factory, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mayor's tax report - Transforming Pittsburgh (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - William Morris Luncheon, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - National League of Cities, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition (NLIHC/LIHIS), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood Needs Program, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - No Way!, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Nuisance bars, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Organizational database (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Parents of Murdered Children, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Patriot Act, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 20)
    1 color, 1 b/w print, 80 35mm negatives, and 44 120 negatives. Subjects consist primarily of Udin portraits but also include City Council and other events Udin was involved with. Includes 1 Sala Udin for Democrat for City Council brochure.
  - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group (PCRG), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group - Vacant Properties Work Group, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, 1996-2003 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Pittsburgh Economic and Industrial Development Corporation (PEIDC), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Pittsburgh Film Office, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Pittsburgh-Minneapolis leadership exchange, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh United Religions Initiative (URI), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - A+ Schools, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - Community Education Partners (CEP), 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - Mayor's Task Force on Education, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - Miller African Centered Academy, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - National Clearinghouse for Comprehensive School Reform (NCCSR) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - Pittsburgh Public School District, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools - Pittsburgh School District - Reports, plans, and presentations, 1998-2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Predatory lending, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Predatory lending - Check cashing and pawn shops, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Public Safety - Fire Bureau - Pittsburgh Fire Fighters Local No. 1, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Programs, pamphlets, and publications, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Public Safety - City of Pittsburgh Police, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Safety - Pittsburgh Police 1992 Statistical Report (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Public Safety - Homicide Task Force, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Public Safety - Human trafficking and involuntary servitude, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Public Safety - Incident reports, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Public Safety - Police recruitment, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Public Safety - Police SWAT policy, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Public Safety - Project Safe Neighborhoods, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Public Safety - Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Police Consent Decree, 2005
    Criminal Justice Statistics, Police Courts, and Prisons: Have We Completely Lost Our Minds?
    Violence Prevention, circa 2002
  - Public Safety - Tasers, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - River-Front Classic and Jamboree, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Riverlife Task Force (RLTF) - Agendas, meetings, and minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Riverlife Task Force - Agendas, meetings, and minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Riverlife Task Force - Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Riverlife Task Force - News and press releases (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Riverlife Task Force - Assessment report, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rivers Club, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Service Employee International Union, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Public Safety - Fraternal Order of Police Lodge No. 1, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Street vacation valuation methodology, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sports and Exhibition Authority, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Talimu CEEP, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Matilda H. Theiss Health Center, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Three Rivers Acts Festival, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Udin at the Democratic National Convention (DNC) - Allegheny County Democratic Party/DNC, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Udin DNC - Certificate of Election, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Udin DNC - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Udin DNC - Electoral college, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Udin DNC - News and photographs (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Udin Elections - Reelection Campaign Fundraising - Boat ride, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Udin Elections - Reelection Campaign Fundraising - Notes and letterhead, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Udin Elections - Reelection Campaign Fundraising - Strip warehouse birthday, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Udin Elections - Reelection Campaign Fundraising - Strip warehouse birthday attendees, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Udin Elections - Results, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Udin Elections - Friends of Sala Udin - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Udin Elections - Friends of Sala Udin - Reception, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Universities - Carnegie Mellon University, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Universities - Carlow College (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Universities - Duquesne University - Dean Search Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Universities - Duquesne University - Master Plan, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Universities - University of Pittsburgh - Benchmark reports, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Universities - University of Pittsburgh - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Universities - University of Pittsburgh - Graduate School of Public and International Affairs, 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Universities - University of Pittsburgh - Institute of Politics, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Urban American, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh (ULP), 1999-2005 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh - Mason Tillman Associates, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 32-33)
  - Vendors - Benchmark Study of Street Vendor Relations, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Vendors - Correspondence and memoranda, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Vendors - Ordinances (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Vendors - Vendors Program, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Voting Rights Act, 30th Anniversary, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - WDUQ, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - WQRD, 1996-2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - We-Hav Program, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Sala Udin Personal Files, 1999-2003; XIII.
  The Sala Udin Personal Files series includes personal records of Councilman Udin between 2001-2004, including phone bills, a biography, travel expense reports, certificates and honors, and material related to his part as George Miles in the theatrical production of "Off the Record."
  - Biography, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Guest Book - Swearing-In Reception, January 7, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Guest Book - Unknown event, February 19, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Guest Book - Unknown event, July 29, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Kudos and certificates (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Off the Record musical (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Udin played George Miles, WQED's chief executive officer.
  - Phone bills, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Travel expense reports, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1995-2005; XIV.
  The Urban Redevelopment Authority (URA) was formed in 1946 and serves as the economic development agency for the City of Pittsburgh. It seeks to generate new jobs and increase the city's tax base to improve business and livability in neighborhoods. It is engaged in various urban renewal efforts including rehabilitation of housing, reclaiming brownfield and former industrial riverfront sites, and business development. The URA is also involved in promoting equal opportunities for minority and female owned businesses. All projects in excess of $250,000 must submit a Minority and Women-Owned Business Enterprise (M/WBE) Plan, which is then reviewed by the URA and the city's M/WBE Review Commission.
  The Urban Redevelopment Authority series is comprised of accomplishment and goal reports; budgets and financial information; M/WBE compliance records; and neighborhood and business (re)development reports and project reviews. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order. This series is primarily comprised of materials recieved by Sala Udin in his capacity of city councilman and as a member on the URA's boad of directors.
  - Accomplishments and goals reports, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 2002 Accomplishments and 2003 Goals report (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 2003 Accomplishments and 2004 Goals report (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 2004 Accomplishments and 2005 Goals (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Administrative budgets, finance, and Act 47 report, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - August Wilson Center for African American Culture (African American Cultural Center) site selection (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - African American Workers Union Funding Proposal report, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Allegheny Institute for Public Policy report and memoranda, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - An Opportunity: A New Commercial Redevelopment in the Heart of Pittsburgh report (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Bedford Proposal and Redevelopment Area Plan Modification #1 report and general Bedford redevelopment URA correspondence, October 2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Crawford Square income studies and Crawford Square Shop 'n Save Supermarket report, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Committee Chair report, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Developers, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - District Improvement Financing (DIF) and Tax Increment Financing (TIF), 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - District Improvement Fund legislation, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Second East Hills, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Employees salary, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Facts sheets for residential conversions in Downtown, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Grocery store / mixed-use urban development project report and correspondence, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Harbor Gardens Greenhouse Project, Manchester, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Hays Woods (5 color prints), 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Hazelwood - Spahr Building, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Hill District - Correspondence to Hill Community Development Corporation regarding Centre Avenue revitalization, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Keystone Opportunity Zone (KOZ), 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Kossman Development regarding Schenley Center, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Includes 1 audio cassette of a Kossman Meeting, February 17, 1997
  - Learta Cooperation Agreement Council, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lazarus' term sheet, 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Budget and Finance Committee report regarding response to Senate Resolution 212, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Living wage legislation, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Lord and Taylor department store, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Mainstreets program, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Meeting agendas, minutes, and notices, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Melody Tent site Option Agreement with SMG Pittsburgh, Inc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Minority / Women's Business Enterprise (M/WBE), 2000-2004 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - M/WBE activities and compliance, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Mulugetta Birru transition notes, July 26, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Neighborhood Needs Program, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - North Avenue structural repairs and Federal North Redevelopment Area proposal report, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - North Shore East / River Avenue redevelopment and Tax Increment Financing plan, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Oak Hill reports, coordinating meeting agenda, and clippings, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    Reports include:
    Beacon/Corcoran Jennison Partners, LLC bound correspondence with Mayor's office, 2000-2003.